<List>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9780575082441</ISBN>
    <Pages>288</Pages>
    <Title>The Last Wish</Title>
    <Year>1993</Year>
    <ImageUrl>TheLastWishsuperNOWA19936903.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>Geralt is a witcher.Yet he is no ordinary killer-for-hire.His sole purpose: to destroy the monsters that plague the world. But not everything monstrous-looking is evil and not everything fair is good. . . and in every fairy tale there is a grain of truth. </Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>4.46</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>10</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9781473211537</ISBN>
    <Pages>384</Pages>
    <Title>Sword of Destiny</Title>
    <Year>1992</Year>
    <ImageUrl>SwordofDestinysuperNOWA19922195.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>Geralt is a witcher, a man whose magic powers, enhanced by long training and a mysterious elixir, have made him a brilliant fighter and a merciless assassin. Yet he is no ordinary murderer: his targets are the multifarious monsters and vile fiends that ravage the land and attack the innocent. This is a collection of short stories, following the adventures of the hit collection THE LAST WISH. Join Geralt as he battles monsters, demons and prejudices alike...</Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>6.63</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9780575084841</ISBN>
    <Pages>320</Pages>
    <Title>Blood of Elves</Title>
    <Year>1994</Year>
    <ImageUrl>BloodofElvessuperNOWA19947417.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>For over a century, humans, dwarves, gnomes, and elves have lived together in relative peace. But times have changed, the uneasy peace is over, and now the races are fighting once again. The only good elf, it seems, is a dead elf.Geralt of Rivia, the cunning assassin known as The Witcher, has been waiting for the birth of a prophesied child. This child has the power to change the world - for good, or for evil.As the threat of war hangs over the land and the child is hunted for her extraordinary powers, it will become Geralt's responsibility to protect them all - and the Witcher never accepts defeat.</Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>6.66</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9780575090941</ISBN>
    <Pages>352</Pages>
    <Title>Time of Contempt</Title>
    <Year>1995</Year>
    <ImageUrl>TimeofContemptsuperNOWA19958664.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>Geralt is a witcher: guardian of the innocent; protector of those in need; a defender, in dark times, against some of the most frightening creatures of myth and legend. His task, now, is to protect Ciri. A child of prophecy, she will have the power to change the world for good or for ill -- but only if she lives to use it.A coup threatens the Wizard's Guild.War breaks out across the lands.A serious injury leaves Geralt fighting for his life...... and Ciri, in whose hands the world's fate rests, has vanished...</Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>12.78</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9780575090972</ISBN>
    <Pages>352</Pages>
    <Title>Baptism of Fire (novel)</Title>
    <Year>1996</Year>
    <ImageUrl>BaptismofFirenovelsuperNOWA19967124.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>The Wizards Guild has been shattered by a coup and, in the uproar, Geralt was seriously injured. The Witcher is supposed to be a guardian of the innocent, a protector of those in need, a defender against powerful and dangerous monsters that prey on men in dark times.But now that dark times have fallen upon the world, Geralt is helpless until he has recovered from his injuries.While war rages across all of the lands, the future of magic is under threat and those sorcerers who survive are determined to protect it. It's an impossible situation in which to find one girl - Ciri, the heiress to the throne of Cintra, has vanished - until a rumor places her in the Niflgaard court, preparing to marry the Emperor.Injured or not, Geralt has a rescue mission on his hands.</Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>12.78</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9788546900886</ISBN>
    <Pages>464</Pages>
    <Title>The Tower of Swallows</Title>
    <Year>1997</Year>
    <ImageUrl>TheTowerofSwallowssuperNOWA19972054.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>The world has fallen into war. Ciri, the child of prophecy, has vanished. Hunted by friends and foes alike, she has taken on the guise of a petty bandit and lives free for the first time in her life.But the net around her is closing. Geralt, the Witcher, has assembled a group of allies determined to rescue her. Both sides of the war have sent brutal mercenaries to hunt her down. Her crimes have made her famous.There is only one place left to run. The tower of the swallow is waiting...</Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>10.87</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9781473211605</ISBN>
    <Pages>544</Pages>
    <Title>The Lady of the Lake</Title>
    <Year>1999</Year>
    <ImageUrl>TheLadyoftheLakesuperNOWA19992830.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>After walking through the portal in the Tower of Swallows while narrowly escaping death, Ciri finds herself in a completely different world... an Elven world. She is trapped with no way out. Time does not seem to exist and there are no obvious borders or portals to cross back into her home world.But this is Ciri, the child of prophecy, and she will not be defeated. She knows she must escape to finally rejoin the Witcher, Geralt, and his companions - and also to try to conquer her worst nightmare. Leo Bonhart, the man who chased, wounded and tortured Ciri, is still on her trail. And the world is still at war.</Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>11.55</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Book>
    <Author>Andrzej Sapkowski</Author>
    <ISBN>9783423260572</ISBN>
    <Pages>384</Pages>
    <Title>Season of Storms</Title>
    <Year>2013</Year>
    <ImageUrl>SeasonofStormssuperNOWA20132102.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>After walking through the portal in the Tower of Swallows while narrowly escaping death, Ciri finds herself in a completely different world... an Elven world. She is trapped with no way out. Time does not seem to exist and there are no obvious borders or portals to cross back into her home world.But this is Ciri, the child of prophecy, and she will not be defeated. She knows she must escape to finally rejoin the Witcher, Geralt, and his companions - and also to try to conquer her worst nightmare. Leo Bonhart, the man who chased, wounded and tortured Ciri, is still on her trail. And the world is still at war.</Description>
    <Country>Poland</Country>
    <Publisher>superNOWA</Publisher>
    <Language>Polish</Language>
    <Price>23.40</Price>
    <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Book>
  <Journal>
    <Frequency>Monthly</Frequency>
    <Title>Archives of Toxicology</Title>
    <Year>2017</Year>
    <ImageUrl>ArchivesofToxicologySpringerScience20174168.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>This proceedings of the European Society of Toxicology Meeting held in Leipzig, September 12 - 14, 1990 deals with the following topics; - Neurotoxicology of different noxious compounds, - New aspects and methods intoxicopathology, - Cardiovascular toxicology, - Toxic effects on haemostasis, - Toxic effects on liver and kidney, - Miscellaneous toxic effects.</Description>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Publisher>Springer Science</Publisher>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <Price>118.00</Price>
    <Genre>Toxicology</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Journal>
  <Journal>
    <Frequency>Monthly</Frequency>
    <Title>Algorithmica</Title>
    <Year>2012</Year>
    <ImageUrl>AlgorithmicaSpringerScience20127070.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>Algorithmica is a monthly peer reviewed, scientific journal, published by Springer Science+Business Media focused on research and application of computer science algorithms. The editor in chief is Ming-Yang Kao. Subject coverage includes sorting, searching, data structures, computational geometry, and linear programming, VLSI, distributed computing, parallel processing, computer aided design, robotics, graphics, data base design, and software tools</Description>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Publisher>Springer Science</Publisher>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <Price>40.30</Price>
    <Genre>Springer Science+Business Media</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Journal>
  <Brochure>
    <Title>Dental Health for Mothers </Title>
    <Year>2008</Year>
    <ImageUrl>DentalHealthforMothersJenniferDarby20089627.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>The birth of your child is a wonderful and exciting time for your family, yet for the nine months of pregnancy leading up to birth, as well as the year after the arrival of your baby, your dental health is at increased risk. Our dentists have a great understanding of the unique challenges you face during this time and have created a page specifically for you. It provides information for mums prior to pregnancy through to after the arrival of your baby.</Description>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Publisher>Jennifer Darby</Publisher>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <Price>15.80</Price>
    <Genre>Dental</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Brochure>
  <Journal>
    <Frequency>Monthly</Frequency>
    <Title>Canadian Family Physician</Title>
    <Year>2017</Year>
    <ImageUrl>CanadianFamilyPhysicianTheCollegeofFamilyPhysiciansofCanada20177774.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>Canadian Family Physician (French: Médecin de famille canadien) is a monthly peer-reviewed open-access medical journal and the official journal of The College of Family Physicians of Canada.</Description>
    <Country>Canada</Country>
    <Publisher> The College of Family Physicians of Canada </Publisher>
    <Language>English, French</Language>
    <Price>25.37</Price>
    <Genre>Family medicine</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Journal>
  <Brochure>
    <Title>See the USA</Title>
    <Year>1999</Year>
    <ImageUrl>SeetheUSATravelCo19996454.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>Liberal, Kansas: "The Pancake Hub of the Universe." Sullivan County, New York: "The lowest death rate of any county in New York State." Rapid City, South Dakota: "The climate is excellent and hog cholera is as yet a stranger." For more than a century, travel brochures have been wooing American "vacationists" with handsome graphics and enticing (and frequently amusing) prose descriptions. See the USA presents more than 200 examples of these delightful documents, drawn from the heyday of American road-tripping. The range of subjects and styles in travel brochure art makes it among the finest work ever produced by American commercial artists, and the descriptions of far-flung destinations are priceless. An entertaining popular culture and design history, See the USA will delight anyone with an interest in the images and words that fueled the patriotic desire to explore the country from coast to coast.</Description>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Publisher>Travel Co</Publisher>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <Price>19.95</Price>
    <Genre>Travel</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Brochure>
  <Brochure>
    <Title>Corvair Sales Brochures</Title>
    <Year>1960</Year>
    <ImageUrl>CorvairSalesBrochuresHITechSoftware19603318.jpg</ImageUrl>
    <Description>Corvair Sales Brochures 1960 - 1969 is a collection of the Chevrolet Corvair sales brochures that chronicle the incredible history of the Corvair. Every page of each piece of literature allows you to zoom in to read all the details for each year. Check out the colors, the specifications, options, photos, sales pitches and much more as presented in each catalog. A must have for any classic Corvair owner or enthusiast! All pages may be copied to the Windows clipboard for subsequent editing and printing in any graphics package.</Description>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Publisher>HI-Tech Software</Publisher>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <Price>12.76</Price>
    <Genre>Cars</Genre>
    <NumbersOfCopies>1</NumbersOfCopies>
  </Brochure>
</List>